export const decks = {
  React: {
    title: 'React',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is a Component?',
        answer:
          'A small, reusable piece of code that returns a React element to be rendered on the page.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What are Props?',
        answer: 'Arbitrary inputs passed as a single object to a component.',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is JSX?',
        answer:
          'A syntax extension in JavaScript that allows mixing XML syntax with JavaScript code.',
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event',
      },
    ],
  },
  JavaScript: {
    title: 'JavaScript',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is a closure?',
        answer:
          'The combination of a function and the lexical environment within which that function was declared.',
      },
    ],
  },
  Redux: {
    title: 'Redux',
    questions: [],
  },
  Architecture: {
    title: 'Architecture',
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'What famous structure in Rome was once used for gladiatorial fights?',
        answer: 'The Colosseum',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the total length of the roadway of the Brooklyn Bridge?',
        answer: '5989 feet',
      },
    ],
  },
  'New York City': {
    title: 'New York City',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is the tallest building in New York City?',
        answer: 'One World Trade Center',
      },
      {
        question: "What is New York City's most common nickname?",
        answer: 'The Big Apple',
      },
      {
        question: 'Who became mayor in 2002',
        answer: 'Michael Bloomberg',
      },
      {
        question: "What is New York City's largest train station?",
        answer: 'Grand Central Terminal',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is located on Broadway between 42nd St and 47th St?',
        answer: 'Times Square',
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the official residence of the Mayor?',
        answer: 'Gracie Mansion',
      },
      {
        question:
          "What theory of policing is often credited with dramatically reducing NYC's crime rate?",
        answer: 'Broken Windows',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Fill in the blanks in the message on the iconic Greek Anthora coffee cup: We are [blank] to [blank] you.',
        answer: 'Happy, Serve',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What’s the only Brooklyn neighborhood that shares its name with a Disney movie?',
        answer: 'Dumbo',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Some New Yorkers keep the females as pets, but it’s illegal to keep the males because of noise. What are we talking about?',
        answer: 'Roosters',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What very popular stage musical is set in New York City, but based on a Shakespeare play?',
        answer: 'West Side Story',
      },
      {
        question:
          'The New York Aquarium is located in which New York City borough?',
        answer: 'Brooklyn',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What stadium located in Flushing, Queens, is home to the New York Mets?',
        answer: 'Shea Stadium',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What building was called the "eighth world wonder" when it was built in 1931?',
        answer: 'Empire State Building',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Where were immigrants entering the United States through the port of New York medically and legally inspected?',
        answer: 'Ellis Island',
      },
      {
        question:
          "New York City is home to the country's largest zoo, which features more than 4,000 animals. What is the name of the zoo?",
        answer: 'Bronx Zoo',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What famous statue was shipped from France in 350 pieces and assembled in New York?',
        answer: 'Statue of Liberty',
      },
      {
        question:
          'In 2007, what contemporary art museum opened their new venue on Bowery Street in Manhattan?',
        answer: 'The New Museum',
      },
      {
        question:
          'What museum in Manhattan, which features 45 permanent exhibition halls, also publishes 10 magazine issues every year?',
        answer: 'American Museum of Natural History',
      },
    ],
  },
};
